<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Erica Ram</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Erica Ram</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2017 ACM Richard Tapia Celebration of Diversity in Computing Conference</title>
      <link>/2017/09/28/tapia-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/09/28/tapia-2017/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend, the 2017 Richard Tapia Celebration of Diversity in Computing Conference took place in Atlanta, GA at the Hyatt Regency Atlanta.
My Microsoft DS3 2016 teammate Louise Y. Lai and I presented our poster on our project Airbrb: Predicting Loyalty. The poster session was held Thursday night for two hours, and for those two hours we had a continuous flow of interested people asking us about our project, much to our delight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goals</title>
      <link>/2017/08/31/goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/08/31/goals/</guid>
      <description>Fall 2017 term has just begun, and I’m interested in setting some goals for myself. My primary goal is to write.
I get really hung up on writing. I can write, but I never want to show it to anyone. I’ve just picked up How to Write a Lot: A Practical Guide to Productive Academic Writing by Paul J. Silva, and I’m hoping that adding structure to the process of writing will help me to write more and to write contents of better quality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello! My name is Erica Ram.
I graduated with a Bachelor of Science in Computer Science, Mathematics minor from Adelphi University in May 2016. I am currently a first year PhD student at University of Alabama in Huntsville.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>/2017/08/15/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/08/15/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello world!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Press</title>
      <link>/press/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/press/</guid>
      <description>Summer school data science research could trigger real world changes (August 2017)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Airbrb: Predicting Loyalty
The advent of the sharing economy has redefined the way firms do business. Airbnb has led this revolution. With a valuation of $25 billion, it has become the world’s third most valued startup and has more rooms than the world’s largest hotel chain. Historically, customer loyalty was based on experience with a particular firm - now, for the sharing economy, it is based on experiences with many individuals.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>